

KEVIN JONATHAN KEILHOFER

Digital Product Designer

📞 +49 176 34059047 🔛 kevin.keilhofer@outlook.com 🄀 kevinkeilhofer.github.io

O Beurenbachweg 3, 73529 Schwäbisch Gmünd, DE

PROFILE

In July 2022 I completed my Bachelor of Arts degree at Schwäbisch Gmünd University of Applied Sciences in the "Internet of Things - Design of Networked Systems" program.

My motivation is to develop products and services that help people solve their problems.

The focus of my motivation is the conception, design and implementation of user-centered products and prototypes. I use design thinking to quickly solve and identify problems, as well as develop innovative ideas that convince and inspire users.

My focus is on UX/UI design, programming and prototyping.

EXPERIENCE

ETAS

March 2021 - Aug 2021

UI & Interaction Designer

Creation of user-centered interaction designs, conducting user research and usability tests, development of concepts and prototypes for future product, etc.

stoba e-Systems GmbH

Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Corporate Communications

Preparation of a presentation folder, blog update on the company website, preparation of text, image, and video material, etc.

Θ

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Bachelor of Arts

HfG Schwäbisch Gmünd

Internet der Dinge - Gestaltung vernetzter Systeme Duration : 2019 - 2022

Fachhochschulreife

Gewerbliche Schule Schwäbisch Gmünd

Technisches Gymnasium: Mechatronik

Duration: 2015 - 2018

☆ TOOLS

ADOBE CREATIVE CLOUD	
FIGMA	
ARDUINO	
SKETCH	
SACION	
HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT	

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Design Thinking
- Teamwork
- Communication

A INTEREST

- Sport
- Technology
- Design Trends
- Development

攻

LANGUAGES

